Be careful of Gu Xingcan.
Um, Lawyer Gu.
This is the newly hired legal counsel.
He will be your assistant from now on.
My assistant?
Got it.
Follow me.
In my previous memory,
this person didn't seem to appear.
He's like a block of wood.
I really don't know how HR finds people.
You don't need to follow me.
Go do your own work.
Gu Xingcan.
Don't come any closer.
Let me go.
I won't hurt you.
I'm here to protect you.
Protect me?
Come here right now.
Y-Your name is?
Chen Yao.
I have something to take care of.
You go...
Get in the car first.
Traitor. I will never trust you again.
Miss Mu.
You're here.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
No matter how much Lingze pays you,
I will pay you more.
Name a price.
Help me win this lawsuit.
Miss Mu, are you trying to make me betray my company?
As long as you help me,
not only will I give you a sum of money,
but I'll also introduce you to a bigger company.
And I promise
you won't have any more worries.
How about it?
I'm sorry.
I am only loyal to my boss.
I didn't expect
you to be such a loyal dog.
Aren't you afraid
that I'll tell everything?
In the end, we'll both go down together.
Miss Mu,
I hope you understand one thing.
The fish might die,
but the net won't necessarily break.
To the company,
you are now nothing but a tool
that is no longer needed after use.
Do you think Mr. Ling
would care about what a worthless tool
has to say?
Look out for yourself.
See you in court.
Who do you think you are
to treat me like this?
Let go.
Do you know who I am?
No matter who you are,
you can't hurt her.
Let go.
Just you wait.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
You didn't tell me where the car was parked.
I don't know if he's a man or a ghost.
It was as if time stood still just now.
Why did those people stop moving?
He said he came to protect me.
He saved me.
How did I come back to this day?
I'll stop thinking about it for now.
The key is to stop Mr. Wang from testifying.
I just need to stay away from him.
What are you doing?
We're here.
Mr. Wang.
Lawyer Gu.
Didn't you say a video testimony would be enough?
I was afraid something might go wrong.
So I'd like to ask you to go in person.
You're so annoying.
If it weren't for Mr. Ling's sake...
Mr. Wang.
We're going to the court to testify.
Do they have to come along?
Witnesses need protection.
Our protection is enough.
Are you capable of that?
Mr. Wang.
The court has rules.
Only witnesses can enter.
Others cannot enter the courtroom without permission.
I'll have them stand at the door.
Why did they hire someone as stubborn as you?
Mr. Wang.
Step aside.
Where is the boss?
What just happened?
How did he get in the car?
How on earth did he do that?
Does the defense wish to make a statement?
Does the defense admit to the plaintiff's accusations?
Please answer.
What's wrong?
I'm fine. It's just a bit hot.
Where to next?
Just drive out of the city first.
As long as this perjury doesn't make it to court,
Lingze won't be able to overturn the case.
Okay.
Can you use this ability infinitely?
My body can't take it if I use it too often.
What's wrong?
This is the guy who threw me into the lake last time.
Smash it.
I'm back again.
Why are you in my house?
How did you get in?
I can go anywhere I want.
These ice creams taste terrible.
Get a different flavor next time.
Who exactly are you?
Who told you to follow me?
Your father.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I am a soul ferryman.
Your father found me
and asked me to protect you.
My dad?
It's up there.
Hand it over.
Stay away from me.
Do it.
Your time in the human world is up.
Come with me.
No.
I can't leave yet.
My daughter still needs me.